PEG taxon name	DynTaxa taxon name
#Aphanocapsa elachista	Aphanocapsa elachista
Actinocyclus octonarius v. crassus	Actinocyclus octonarius var. crassus
Actinocyclus octonarius v. octonarius	Actinocyclus octonarius var. octonarius
Actinocyclus octonarius v. tenellus	Actinocyclus octonarius var. tenellus
Amphiprora paludosa v. paludosa	Amphiprora paludosa var. paludosa
Aphanothece paralleliformis	Aphanothece parallelliformis
Aulacoseira granulata v. angustissima	Aulacoseira granulata var. angustissima
Aulacoseira granulata v. granulata	Aulacoseira granulata var. granulata
Chaetoceros anastomosans v. externa	Chaetoceros anastomosans var. externa
Chaetoceros ceratosporus v. ceratosporus	Chaetoceros ceratosporus var. ceratosporus
Chaetoceros didymus v. anglica	Chaetoceros didymus var. anglica
Chaetoceros didymus v. didymus	Chaetoceros didymus var. didymus
Chaetoceros didymus v. protuberans	Chaetoceros didymus var. protuberans
#Chaetoceros salsugineus	Chaetoceros salsugineus
Chaetoceros subtilis v. subtilis	Chaetoceros subtilis var. subtilis
Chaetoceros throndsenii v. throndsenii	Chaetoceros throndsenii var. throndsenii
Closterium acutum v. acutum	Closterium acutum var. acutum
Closterium acutum v. variabile	Closterium acutum var. variabile
Cocconeis placentula v. placentula	Cocconeis placentula var. placentula
Cocconeis scutellum v. scutellum	Cocconeis scutellum var. scutellum
Desmodesmus armatus v. armatus	Desmodesmus armatus var. armatus
Desmodesmus armatus v. bicaudatus	Desmodesmus armatus var. bicaudatus
Desmodesmus armatus v. spinosus	Desmodesmus armatus var. spinosus
Desmodesmus denticulatus v. denticulatus	Desmodesmus denticulatus var. denticulatus
Desmodesmus denticulatus v. linearis	Desmodesmus denticulatus var. linearis
Desmodesmus opoliensis v. opoliensis	Desmodesmus opoliensis var. opoliensis
Diatoma vulgaris v. vulgaris	Diatoma vulgaris var. vulgaris
Fragilaria capucina v. capucina	Fragilaria capucina var. capucina
Gomphonema olivaceum v. olivaceum	Gomphonema olivaceum var. olivaceum
Heterocapsa arctica ssp. frigida	Heterocapsa arctica ssp. frigida
#Katablepharis remigera	Katablepharis remigera
Lagerheimia longiseta v. longiseta	Lagerheimia longiseta var. longiseta
Licmophora gracilis v. gracilis	Licmophora gracilis var. gracilis
#Lobocystis planctonica	Lobocystis planctonica
Mastogloia smithii v. smithii	Mastogloia smithii var. smithii
Meridion circulare v. circulare	Meridion circulare var. circulare
#Mesoporus perforatus	Mesoporus perforatus
#Microcystis ichtyoblabe	Microcystis ichtyoblabe
Navicula capitata v. capitata	Navicula capitata var. capitata
Navicula capitata v. hungarica	Navicula capitata var. hungarica
Navicula peregrina v. peregrina	Navicula peregrina var. peregrina
Navicula transitans v. deresa f. delicatula	Navicula transitans var. derasa f. delicatula
Navicula transitans v. transitans	Navicula transitans var. transitans
Navicula viridula v. viridula	Navicula viridula var. viridula
Nitzschia acicularis v. acicularis	Nitzschia acicularis var. acicularis
Pediastrum angulosum v. angulosum	Pediastrum angulosum var. angulosum
Pediastrum boryanum v. boryanum	Pediastrum boryanum
Pediastrum boryanum v. longicorne	Pediastrum boryanum var. longicorne
Pediastrum duplex v. duplex	Pediastrum duplex var. duplex
Prorocentrum redfieldii	Prorocentrum redfeldii
#Rhabdoderma lineare	Rhabdoderma lineare
Rhodomonas lacustris v. lacustris	Rhodomonas lacustris var. lacustris
Rhodomonas lacustris v. nannoplanctica	Rhodomonas lacustris var. nannoplanctica
#Scenedesmus acutiformis	Scenedesmus acutiformis
Scenedesmus arcuatus v. arcuatus	Scenedesmus arcuatus var. arcuatus
#Schroederia setigera	Schroederia setigera
#Selenastrum bibraianum	Selenastrum bibraianum
#Selenastrum gracile	Selenastrum gracile
#Spatulodinium pseudonoctiluca	Spatulodinium pseudonoctiluca
Staurosira construens v. binodis	Staurosira construens var. binodis
Staurosira construens v. construens	Staurosira construens var. construens
Staurosira construens v. venter	Staurosira construens var. venter
#Synechococcus	Synechococcus
Synedra acus v. acus	Synedra acus var. acus
Synedra ulna v. ulna	Synedra ulna var. ulna
Thalassiosira hyperborea v. pelagica	Thalassiosira hyperborea var. pelagica
Centrales	Coscinodiscophyceae
Craspedophyceae	Choanoflagellidea
Pennales	Bacillariophyceae